ahmedabadcity.gov.in 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy :: Ahmedabad Municipal Corporation

Ahmedabad Municipal Corporation (AMC) has built the Ahmedabad AMC app as a personalized app for Ahmedabad citizen. This SERVICE is provided by Ahmedabad Municipal Corporation (AMC) at no cost and is intended for use as is. This page is used to inform application users regarding organizationâ€™s policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service. If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Ahmedabad AMC unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy. 

Personal Information:

Camera, Phone Contacts and Device Information use for a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to email account User Data or Device Information. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. 

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app 

We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (â€œIPâ€) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

Cookies

This Service does not use these â€œcookiesâ€ explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use â€œcookiesâ€ to collection information and to improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

Security

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Sites

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children Privacy

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions. 

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If for some reason you believe AMC has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at info@ahmedabadcity.gov.in, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. 

Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.
